Guide to American University Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00064
Cubberley Education Library
American University
1894-1980
Cubberley Education Library
Cubb.00064
165 item(s)
Located in Washington, D.C. Founded in 1893 by Methodist bishop John Fletcher Hurst. Affilated with the Methodist Church.
Washington, D.C.
- The University Courier, 1894-1908; 45 item(s) Vol 2, no. 4, 1894; vol. 3, nos. 1, 3, 4, 1894/95; Vol. 4, nos. 3 & 4, 1896; Vol. 5, nos. 1-4, 1896/97; Vol. 6, nos. 1-4, 1897/98; Vol. 7, nos. 1-3, 1898/99' Vol. 8, nos. 1-4, 1900/01, Vol. 9, nos. 1-2, 4, 1901/02; Vol. 10, nos. 1-4, 1903/04; Vol 11, nos. 1-4, 1904/05; Vol. 12, nos. 2-4, 1905/06; Vol. 13, nos. 1-4, 1906/07; Vol. 14, nos. 1-4, 1907/08; Vol. 15, nos. 1-3, 1908
- The American University Courier, 1910-1926; 43 item(s) Vol. 17, nos. 1-4, 1910/11; Vol. 18, nos. 1-4, 1911/12; Vol. 19, nos. 2 & 4, 1912/13; Vol. 20, nos. 1, 3 & 4, 1913/14; Vol. 21, nos. 2 & 4, 1914/15; Vol. 22, nos. 1 & 3, 1915/16; Vol. 23, nos. 3-4, 1917; Vol. 24, nos. 1-2 & 4, 1917/18; Vol. 25, nos. 1-2 & 4, 1918/19; Vol. 26, nos. 1-4, 1919/20; Vol. 27, nos. 1-3, 1920/21; Vol. 28, nos. 1-3, 1921/22; Vol. 29, nos. 1-2 & 4, 1922/23; Vol. 30, nos. 1 & 3, 1924; Vol. 31, nos. 1 & 4, 1925; Vol. 32, no. 1, 1926
- American University, 1914-1980; 20 item(s) Announcements for 1914/16, 1923/24-1925/26 (Special issues of American University Courier) Catalogs for 1935/36-1937/38, 1940/41-1942/43, 1953/56, 1956/59, 1962/63, 1963/64-1964/65, 1969/70-1970/71, 1972/73, 1975/77, 1978/80 (Special issues of American University Bulletin)
- American Unversity School of Diplomacy, Jurisprudence, and Citizenship, 1920-21; 1 item(s) Circular for 1920/21
- American University College of Liberal Arts, 1925-1939; 11 item(s) Catalogs for 1925/26-1928/29, 1930/31-1934/35, 1938/39
- American University School of the Political Sciences, 1925-1932; 5 item(s) Catalogs for 1925/26-1928/29 (published with Graduate School), 1930/31-1931/32
- American University Graduate School, 1925-1966; 10 item(s) Announcements for 1925/26, 1927/28-1929/30 Catalogs for 1930/31-1931/32, 1956/59, 1960/63, 1962/64, 1964/66 Courses for 1934/35
- American University Charter and By-Laws Number, December, 1929; 1 item(s)
- Graduate Study of Government, April, 1930; 1 item(s)
- American University School of Public Affairs, 1936-37; 1 item(s) Announcement for 1936/37
- American University Graduate School in the Social Sciences, 1937-38; 1 item(s) Announcement for 1937/38
- American University Undergraduate Bulletin, 1939-40; 1 item(s) Catalog for 1939/40
- American University College of Arts and Sciences, 1945-1967; 5 item(s) Catalog for 1949/50, 1958/61, 1963/65, 1966/67 Bulletin for Fall Semester 1945
- American University Washington College of Law, 1950-1963; 7 item(s) Catalog for 1950/51, 1952/53-1960/63
- Announcement of Courses in Record and Archives Administration, 1951-52; 1 item(s) Typescript list of courses.
- Annual Reports of the President and the Treasurer, 1955-1962; 3 item(s) Reports for 1955/56, 1960/61-1961/62
- American University School of International Service, 1958-1966; 3 item(s) Catalogs for 1958/61, 1962/64-1964/66
- American University School of Government and Public Administration, 1960-1966; 3 item(s) Catalogs for 1960/63, 1962/64-1964/66
- American University School of Business Administration, 1962-1966; 2 item(s) Catalogs for 1962/64, 1965/66
- American University Summer Session, 1963; 1 item(s) Catalog for 1963